<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>post1 &#8211; NguyenLuan++</title>
	<atom:link href="https://nguyenluan01.github.io/whysoeasy/tu-khoa-san-pham/post1/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://nguyenluan01.github.io/whysoeasy</link>
	<description>Chúc mừng bạn đã được thêm tên vào DeaThnOte</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 13:09:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>13 oz Ceramic Mug in Natural</title>
		<link>https://nguyenluan01.github.io/whysoeasy/product/13-oz-ceramic-mug-in-natural/</link>
					<comments>https://nguyenluan01.github.io/whysoeasy/product/13-oz-ceramic-mug-in-natural/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nguyenluan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 02:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://nguyenluan01.github.io/whysoeasy/?post_type=product&#038;p=1195</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<strong>Product Specs:</strong>
ø3.37″ x 3.5″ / 13 oz
Porcelain

Designed by Takuhiro Shinomoto of Hasami Porcelain with “texture, simplicity, and usability” in mind, their products are a perfect representation of the modern Japanese aesthetic. The brand takes its name from the historic town of Hasami of Nagasaki prefecture, renowned for its pottery, in Japan, where craftsmen have been producing porcelainware for 400 years.

This mug has come a long way from its roots.

&#160;
<ul>
 	<li>Made in Japan</li>
 	<li>Microwave and dishwasher safe</li>
 	<li>Not safe for oven use</li>
</ul>
*Manufacture environment of the porcelain varies depending on season or kiln temperatures. Every piece has the character of quality hand-made porcelain. Therefore, variances in shapes, sizes, and colors can sometimes happen.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embodying the raw, wayward spirit of rock ‘n’ roll, the Kilburn portable active stereo speaker takes the unmistakable look and sound of Marshall, unplugs the chords, and takes the show on the road.</p>
<p>Weighing in under 7 pounds, the Kilburn is a lightweight piece of vintage styled engineering. Setting the bar as one of the loudest speakers in its class, the Kilburn is a compact, stout-hearted hero with a well-balanced audio which boasts a clear midrange and extended highs for a sound that is both articulate and pronounced. The analogue knobs allow you to fine tune the controls to your personal preferences while the guitar-influenced leather strap enables easy and stylish travel.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://nguyenluan01.github.io/whysoeasy/product/13-oz-ceramic-mug-in-natural/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
